他们现在想在酒吧里干了吗
Now they want to do this Sorry at a bar?
外面怎么了  中间地带更好吧
What happened to outside? Somewhere more neutral.
我的人在他们那边
Man, my connection's on their side.
但我们不会有事的
But we'll be good.
你没意见吗
You cool with this?
拉马尔说没事就没事
Lamar say we good, we good.
你三周来也了解他一些了
You known him a little over three weeks.
他还是你最好的朋友吗
And already this your best friend?
马利克  别废话了
Malik, talk a little less,
多听听你哥的话
listen to your brother more.
他显然有很强的判断力
He's obviously a terrific judge of character.
我们走吧
Let's get this done.
好东西在后面  我们继续走
Party's in the back. Let's keep it moving.
下午好
Afternoon.
看到阿特沃特了
Got eyes on Atwater.
他朝后边走了
He's headed towards the back room.
怎么样啊  瑞恩
How we doin'? What up, Ryan?
-你迟到了  -我对
- You're late. - I don't know my way
卡纳里镇不熟  你懂的
around Canaryville like that. You know that, bro.
滑稽镇吧
More like Crackerville.
是啊
Yeah, right.
你说什么
What did you say?
没什么  马利克就是开玩笑
Nah, man, Malik just be playin', bro.
你很有幽默感
You're a funny dude.
只是开玩笑
Just playin'.
对  那是他兄弟  沙巴兹
Yeah, bro, and that's his brother, Shabazz.
我跟你提过
He's my dude I told you about.
好  这事戴克斯特
All right, cool. This is Dexter.
-他是他表兄内特  -你们好
- That's his cousin, Nate. - What's up, gentlemen?
好了  那些M4在哪
All right, so where the M4s at?
我们先喝一杯怎么样
Why don't we get a drink, you know?
打一会儿桌球
Play a little nine-ball.
先互相熟悉一下
Get to know each other a little better.
我们只是来做生意的
We just came to do business.
不是来开茶话会的
Not have a tea party.
我想了解我的生意伙伴
I like to know who I work with.
搞什么
What's this?
搞什么  你们在耍我们吗
Yo, what's up, man, trying to play us like a bunch of punks.
说话小心点
Watch yourself.
Watch myself?
好了  冷静
All right, chill, man.
你亲自来教教我怎么说话啊
Why don't you make me watch myself?
马利克  冷静点
Yo, Malik, man, chill out.
-等等  -冷静  老兄
- Yo, hey, hey, yo! - Easy, come on, man.
你们在干什么
The hell are you doin' man?
警长  后面房间有动静
Sarge, we got action in the back room.
按兵不动  没人说安全词
Just stand down. No one said the safe word.
让阿特沃特和霍斯特德来处理
Let Atwater and Halstead handle it.
怎么回事  老兄
Hell is this, man?
我们只是来拿枪
We just came to get these guns
然后就走  你可以先把枪放下吗
and get out your way. You wanna put that down?
我只是在给马利克看货
I'm just showing Malik the merchandise.
M4-A1卡宾  全自动
M4-A1 carbine, fully automatic.
三秒内30发
30 rounds in three seconds.
好了  老兄  把枪放下
Hey, come on, man. Cut it out.
切入坦克外壳
Cuts through the side of a tank
就像切黄油一样
like a stick of butter.
想象一下如果是你的脑袋会如何
Imagine what it would do to your head.
你这么厉害那就开枪啊
You so tough, pull the trigger.
伙计们  我们...
Look, guys, let's, um--
我们喝一杯吧  先玩一把
Let's get that drink, huh? Let's play some pool.
来吧
Come on, man.
我们不和这些蠢货玩桌球
We ain't finna play pool with these punk-ass bitches.
-老兄  -行了  伙计
- Dude! - Come on, bro,
你知道没必要这样
you know that was uncalled for.
-谁才是蠢货  -拜托...
- Who's the bitch now? - Hey, come on, man--
-道歉  -算了
- Say you're sorry. - Yo, just leave it!
我要他说
I want him to say it.
我才不会道歉
I'm not saying nothin'.
你不值得我浪费子弹  蠢货
You ain't worth the bullet, bitch.
我们走  我们离开这里
Come on, let's go. Nah, we out of here.
我们走  走
Let's go, let's go!
我们快走
Come on! Here we go.
杰
Jay!
怎么回事
What the hell is going on, man?
我们去做生意  他们玩什么呢
We came in to make a deal. What they playin' games for?
等等  我们这边也莫名其妙好吗
Hold up, man! It was a go on our side, too, all right?
让你的人安分点
Get your boy in line!
-真的吗  -等等  你们拿到枪了吧
- Really, dawg? - Hey, wait, your guys have the guns, right?
内特拿的哪把肯定是M4
The gun that Nate pulled was definitely an M4,
我只知道这么多
that much I know.
但我不知道他们具体有多少
I don't know how many they actually have, though.
好吧  所以这些人要不就是很谨慎
All right, so were these guys being careful,
要不就是在拖延时间
or were they just trying to buy time
因为手上没有足够的枪支
'cause they don't have the guns in their possession?
不清楚  戴克斯特做事太小心了
It's unclear--Dexter plays everything close to the vest.
好吧  我们继续关注这事
Okay, so let's keep this thing alive.
好吗  杰  凯文  你们继续卧底
All right? Jay, Kevin, you stay under.
努力促成这次枪支交易
Try to make this gun deal happen.
好吗  我们必须要缴了这批M4
'Kay? We have gotta get these M4s off the street.
杀伤力太强了
They're too powerful.
我们走
Let's go.
你来干什么
What the hell do you want?
坏消息  阿尔  陪审团投票结果是起诉
Bad news, Al. Grand jury voted to indict.
你因谋杀凯文·宾汉姆而被捕了
You're under arrest for the murder of Kevin Bingham.
站起来
Stand up.
我们要没收你的武器和警徽
We're gonna need your weapon and badge.
什么  你们开什么玩笑  用手铐
What, are you kidding me? Handcuffs?
他从警三十年了
He's got 30 years on the job.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
武器和警徽  现在就上交
Weapon. And badge. Now.
翻译     西之   不高兴童鞋   风城章鱼X
慢点
Slowly.
翻译     小萝莉   Lynn_宁   H小欠   圈圈
校对     圈圈
时间轴     chance-coco   西查
后期     8T
总监     圈圈
走吧
Let's go.
不用担心
I got this.
芝加哥
警署
第五季
第二十一集
3942号诉讼案件
Docket 3942.
伊利诺斯州对埃尔文·奥林斯基提起公诉
People of the state of Illinois vs. Alvin Olinsky,
单次二级谋杀
single count of murder in the second degree
以及故意隐瞒杀人罪
and felony concealment of a homicide.
法官阁下  我是辩方律师皮特·玛奈提
Your honor, Peter Manetti for the defendant.
你们将如何申辩
How does your client plead?
无罪
Not guilty.
我申请被告人
I'd like to request that the defendant be released
取保候审
on his own recognizance.
他是一位授过勋的警官  警龄超过30年
He's a decorated police officer, with over 30 ye--
保释听证会是在两天后  律师
Bond hearing is in two days, counselor.
那时再说吧  下一个案件
Give your speech then. Next case.
跟我来
Come with me.
埃尔  埃尔  拜托
Al, Al, please.
-你现在必须结束这一切  -我们走
- You've gotta end this now. - Let's go.
4523号诉讼案件
Docket Number 4523,
伊利诺斯州对唐纳德·奥德姆提起公诉
people of the state of Illinois vs. Donald Odem.
三次殴打重罪
Three counts of felony battery.
-控方辩方都到场了吗  -是的  法官阁下
- All parties present? - Yes, Your Honor.
你准备好开口了吗  汉克
So, you ready to talk, Hank?
你知道奥林斯基是无辜的
You know Olinksy's innocent.
你知道他没有杀那个人渣宾汉姆
You know he didn't kill that piece of garbage, Bingham.
是吗  那是谁杀的
Oh, yeah? Then who did?
奥林斯基要么背叛  要么就把牢底坐穿
Olinsky flips or he rots in prison.
我知道  我知道
I know, I know.
浅褐色不适合我
Beige isn't my color.
你不会穿太久的  我保证
You're not gonna have to wear it long, I promise.
我没事
Nah, I'm good.
他们根本无法立案
I mean, they don't have a case.
证据并不充分  这我们都知道
The evidence is weak. We all know that.
我会申请保释  然后再从长计议
I'll make bail. We go from there.
听着
Okay, listen.
我会给你雇一位律师
I'm hiring a lawyer.
-我会带你离开这里  -我不想这样
- I'm getting you out of here. - I don't want that.
埃尔  我并不在乎你想怎样
Al...I don't really care what you want.
听我说  你就帮我获得保释资格就行了
Listen, man, just make sure I get bail.
明白吗  我就这一个要求
All right? That's all I ask.
我们经历过更困难的处境
I mean, we've been through worse.
每一次我们都能找到解决的办法
And every time, we find a way through to the other side.
这一次  也没什么不一样
All right? Listen, man, this is no different.
我很感谢你的忠诚  可是...
Yeah. Listen. I appreciate your loyalty, but--
我们会...我们能赢的
Hey, we're gonna-- We can beat this.
一定能赢
We will beat it.
这里可是芝加哥
All right? It's Chicago.
我需要点东西
I need something.
-奥林斯基  -保释听证会在两天后
- Olinsky. - Listen, the bail hearing is in two days.
我并不在乎要多少钱
I mean, I don't care what the number is.
我只要保证他能出来
I just need to make sure he gets out.
我们这说的可是谋杀  汉克
Talking about murder here, Hank.
我们这说的是一名警察  汤米
We're talking about a cop here, Tommy.
是啊
Yeah.
现在这个时代  警察的身份可能不是件好事
These days, that might work against him.
你知道外面人都怎么说
You know what the hell it's like out there.
我不在乎  你明白吗
I don't care what it's like. You understand?
我只要他被释放
I just need to make sure he gets released.
不
No.
我需要你
I need you...
让他离开监狱
to make sure he gets released.
汉克  你这是强人所难
Hank, this is a really hard ask.
你知道什么才叫强人所难吗
You know what's a hard ask?
装作没看到一位备受尊敬的法官
Looking the other way when a respected judge
开枪杀死一个毒贩
shoots a drug dealer in cold blood.
他杀了我的女儿  那是他活该
He killed my daughter. He got what he deserved.
我知道  我也同意
Yeah, I know. And I agree.
所以我才放过了你
That's why you got a pass.
汤米
Tommy...
我需要他被释放  你明白吗
I need this. You understand? So...
无论你要做什么  麻烦你
Whatever you have to do, just...
让埃尔有资格获得保释
Make sure Al makes bail.
-有新消息吗  警长  -保释听证会在两天之后
- Any update, Sarge? - Yep, bond hearing's in two days.
他到时会被释放
He'll be released then.
这我可说不准
I don't know about that.
我能说的准
Well, I do.
我说了他到时会被释放
I said, he'll be released then.
还有问题的话
Any more questions?
现在就赶紧问
Now's the time.
听着
Listen...
我得承认  这一天
I'm not gonna lie. It has been...
确实不好过
A tough day.
但我们还有自己的工作要做  明白吗
But we still have jobs to do, right?
地球还在继续运转
The world continues to turn.
所以
So.
那批M4卡宾枪查到什么了吗
Who's got an update on these M4s?
我刚和霍斯特德聊过  他确认那些枪
I just talked to Halstead. He confirmed Dexter
并不属于戴克斯特
did not have the guns in his possession.
他们本该昨天把枪送走的
They were supposed to be dropped off yesterday,
可是他在印第安纳州的接头人出了问题
but his connect in Indiana got hung up.
所以改到了今天
They will be dropped off today.
好  知不知道他的接头人是谁
Okay. Do we know who his connect is?
-还不知道  -好  阿特沃特
- Not at this point. - All right, Atwater,
你的那几个帮派朋友  他们信任你吗
These bangers you're hanging with, do they trust you?
沙巴兹信我  我救过他的命
Yeah, Shabazz does. I saved his life.
当时是我举着枪威胁他的  不过随便了
Well, I was the guy holding the gun threatening him, but.
不如我们重新谈一下之前的交易
So, how about we get this deal back on track?
好  他们都听一个叫韦斯的人的命令
Okay, well, they answer to this dude named Wes.
一切都是韦斯拍板
Wes calls all the shots.
而他手下刚刚被白人给揍了
And his boys just got punked by some white dudes,
所以他气死了  不过我能对付
so he's hot as hell, but...I got it.
很好
Good.
-来吧  -好
- You good? - Yeah, uh-huh.
等等  你想让我忘了这事
So wait a minute, you want me to overlook what happened?
满脸陪笑吗  还把另一边脸
Just smile? Turn the other cheek
舔上去让他们揍个痛快吗
and let them boys just piss all over us?
哥们  我可没这么说
Homie, I ain't never sayin' that.
那你什么意思  你什么意思你
Then what you sayin', then? What is you sayin'?
这事还有啥好说的
Why we even discussing this?
他们把我们像傻子一想耍
They played us like some damn fools.
要我说就该过去给他们点颜色看看
I say we go over there and do what's right.
你想怎样  杀人吗
What, you wanna start killing people?
-没错  -这样没好处
- You damn right. - There's no profit in that.
而且也太惹事了
And it'll bring too much heat.
至少让我把那个白人小子内特给做了
Well, at least let me square away the white boy, Nate.
那个混蛋以为我们是那样好欺负的吗
Cracker think it's okay to violate me like that, us?
我知道你没问我  韦斯
Look, I know you ain't askin' me, Wes,
但我总觉得我们想得不对
but I feel like we missing a big move right here.
我们还复什么仇呢  为什么不把
Now why would we get revenge, when we could just use
整件事  我们挨的打
that whole situation, that whole beat-down,
当成我们的筹码呢
as some kind of bargaining chip or something?
让我再去和戴克斯特谈谈
Let me go over there and talk to Dexter.
我跟他说你怒了
I'll tell him that you pissed off.
他自然就会以为你要报复
Naturally he expected you to clap back,
但你比那高明  是吧
but you smarter than that, right?
你也不是个事儿逼  你是个生意人
You ain't no bitch. You a business man,
生意人就是肚大能容
and a business man is willing to overlook
愿意放过打人的事
this whole Malik situation,
只要他愿意为了这事给你个折扣
if he down to give you a discount on the heaters,
而且整桩生意都在你俱乐部
and do the whole deal right here in your club
在你的地盘做的话  哥们  咱们就赢了
where you comfortable. Come on, boy, we win.
这主意上道
That's what's up.
你说真的  你们都认真的吗
What, is you serious? Y'all serious?
我需要你别掺和
I'm gonna need you to back off.
不准报复  什么都不做  明白了吗
No retaliation, no nothing. We clear?
哥们  难道我就要
Yo, my man. I'm supposed to just
让他们把我当个婊子一样吆喝吗
let him talk to me like some type of bitch?
马利克
Malik.
我不说第二次
I ain't gon' ask you again, man.
明白了吗
Are we clear?
明白了
Yeah, we clear.
非常明白
Loud and clear.
那就好
Cool.
我这就联系戴克斯特
Let me hit Dexter now.
不了  我联系他
No. I'll hit him up.
走中间人我没耐心等
I'm tired of dealing with the middle man.
只要能拿到我那份  我就没意见
All right, as long as I get my cut, I ain't trippin'.
放心你肯定拿得到
Oh, you gon' get your cut.
我说话算话
I'm a man of my word.
厉害啊你  没想到韦斯
I'm impressed. No way I thought Wes would
还愿意把这生意做下去
still be open to doing business.
我说了  他是个聪明人
I told you, man. He's smart.
也没那么聪明  哪怕打八折
He ain't that smart. Even with the 20% discount,
这傻子付的钱还是比市价高一半
dumbass is still paying 50% over market.
不过这样挺好
It's good, though.
如果这次谈成了
You know, if this works out,
我们就能通过韦斯卖给其他黑人帮派
we can use Wes to distribute to the other black gangs.
怎么说  通过内特打进他们内部吗
So what's up, the guns are inside with Nate?
这你不用管
That's not your concern.
我只是想把这桩交易顺利做完
I'm just trying to make sure we do the deal right.
至少这次是这样
This time, anyway.
别紧张  一切都会顺利的
Relax, it's all gonna work out.
内特
Yo, Nate!
该走了哥们  办正事去了
Let's go, man, it's game time!
你来看
Yo, check this out.
这帮混蛋想开战
Those punks want to start a war,
可是找对人了
they came to the right place.
他们一小时前就该到了
They're supposed to be here an hour ago.
是啊  我们都明白
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I know, we got you.
我早说过了
Keep telling y'all.
那些人一点都不尊重人  不值得信任
Dudes don't respect nothing. They can't be trusted.
-我来说就行  -好
- Let me do this, man. - Got it.
我能行  莱恩
I got it. Ryan?
怎么回事啊  这都等你呢哥们
What the hell is goin' on, man? We waitin' on you, bro.
好吧
All right.
怎么回事
What happened?
这交易今天是谈不成了
That deal ain't going down today.
怎么说
Why not?
内特被人弄死了
Nate just popped up dead.
拜托你告诉我
Please tell me
你没我想的那么蠢
you ain't as stupid as I think you are.
当然没  这跟我一点关系没有
Hell no, I ain't had nothing to do with that.
-你确定吗  -绝对确定
- You sure about that? - I'm positive!
今天你刚刚跟我申请过
You asked permission earlier today
想宰掉个叫内特的混蛋枪贩子
to pop off some cracker-ass gun seller named Nate.
而到了晚上  这个枪贩子
And tonight, that same cracker-ass gun seller
就死了  还跟你一点关系都没有吗
wind up dead, and it ain't got nothin' to do with you?
韦斯你别激动
Wes, chill man.
事情就这样  纯粹是巧合
It is what it is, man. It's just a coincidence.
我可不信什么巧合
Well, I don't believe in coincidence, man.
沙巴兹  你相信巧合吗
Shabazz, you--you believe in coincidence, man?
我也不确定
Not sure, all right?
但我知道人不是马利克杀的
Man, I know Malik didn't do the murder.
-怎么说  -因为你不让他杀
- Why you say that? - 'Cause you told him not to.
而且我今天一直跟他在一起
All right, 'cause I was with him all day.
一直看着他
Never left my sight.
而我没见着他杀过什么叫内特的白人小子
And I ain't seen him kill no white boy named Nate.
韦斯  真不是我杀的
Yo! Wes, I didn't do it, man!
你最好希望...最好希望
You better hope... You better hope
他说的是真话  老兄
he's telling the truth, man.
枪支买卖
当然马利克不供认了
Of course Malik didn't cop to it.
他一直发誓和这事无关
Man swore up and down he had nothing to do with it.
也是很令人信服了
Almost convincing, too.
-你信他吗  -一点也不信
- You believe him? - Not for a second.
好  那我们去申请一张马利克家的搜查令
All right, so let's get a search warrant for Malik's house.
也许能发现些血迹  枪支
Maybe we find some blood, a gun.
那样能立一个谋杀案
Build a murder case that way.
我们现在行动  就是毁了阿特沃特的卧底身份
We go in now, we blow Atwater's cover.
我知道  但我们说的可是谋杀案
I know, but, you know, we're talking murder.
我可不会基于一个"可能"搞黄一起枪支大案
I'm not gonna blow a major gun case on a "Maybe."
那现在怎样  坐等
So now what? Sit back and wait
戴克斯特和他的人挑起帮派争斗吗
for Dexter and his boys to start a gang war?
希望对于那事他够聪明
Well, hopefully he's too smart for that.
我不那么确定  警长
I'm not so sure, Sarge.
他眼里都是怒火
He had fire in his eyes.
说自己要杀了所有相关的人
He said he was gonna kill everybody involved.
和他聊聊
Talk to him.
劝他像商人那样思考
Persuade him to think like a businessman.
喂
Hey, man.
给你准备了私人牢房
Got your own private room.
希望你不会呆太久
Hopefully you won't be here long.
你可能知道
Look, you probably know this,
警察在这里是靶子
but cops are targets around here,
所以我个人会尽可能帮忙
so I'm gonna personally do what I can to help out.
我一直想做个警察
I always wanted to be a cop myself.
狱警是第二选择
Corrections was the next best thing.
-好  -还有件事
- Right. - Oh, one more thing.
你不会想要吃饭的
You don't wanna eat the food,
因为这些畜生会在上面撒尿
because these animals are gonna piss in it.
谢谢
Thanks.
我会罩着你的
I got your back.
你就是那头猪
So you're the pig?
一切都会来的
It's coming.
只是时间关系
Just a matter of time.
我们还会找到你老婆
And we're gonna find your wife, too.
再提到我老婆  我宰了你
You ever mention my wife again, I'll kill you.
-退后  -我要杀了你  杀了你
- Hey! Back it up! - I'll kill you, I'll kill you.
-放开他  -我要杀了你
- Let him go! - I'll kill you.
好消息  我刚得知
There's good news. I just got word
格拉德查克法官负责
that Judge Gladchuck is in charge
明天的保释听证会
of bail hearings tomorrow.
格拉德查克  他是个硬派人物
Gladchuck? He's a hard-ass.
我知道
I know.
明天  他不会来
Tomorrow, he's not gonna be there.
他会得肠胃炎
He's gonna contract the stomach flu.
很严重的
The really bad kind.
发烧  恶心之类的
Fever, nausea, the whole thing.
-真可惜  -是啊
- Oh, that's a shame. - Yeah.
可能要到8:55左右才会这样
It's probably not gonna hit him till 8:55 or so,
就在出庭之前  那时候他会找我
just before court convenes, at which point he'll reach out,
让我顶替他  我会欣然同意
ask me to cover for him. And I will graciously agree.
你确定他会找你吗
You sure he's gonna come through?
他别无选择
Doesn't have a choice.
你有他的把柄
You got something on him.
我有所有人的把柄
I got something on everybody.
和你一样
Just like you.
谢了  汤米
Thanks, Tommy.
-芝加哥的春天  -是啊
- Spring in Chicago, huh? - Yeah.
再说一次  瑞安
Say what you said one more time, Ryan.
Say what you said one more time, Ryan,
我觉得我没听明白
'cause I don't think I heard you right.
所以再说一次
So say it one more time.
我觉得你还是应该继续和韦斯他们的交易
I think you should still do the deal with Wes' crew.
无视他们杀了我表兄的事实吗
And ignore the fact they killed my cousin?
我没这么说
I didn't say that.
好  这么说吧
All right, hold up.
是他们杀的人
Let's say they did the murder.
你要复仇  那也得是交易
You're gonna get revenge, you're gonna do it
之后  而不是之前
after we do the deal, not before.
你有7天的时间给供应商付清款项吗
You got, what, seven days to pay off the supplier?
这有什么关系
And what has that got to do with anything?
是的  如果你是牛仔作风  揍马利克一顿
Right, if you go cowboy and you pop Malik
或是沙巴兹一顿  警察肯定要找上你
or you pop Shabazz, the cops are gonna be all over you.
那你就没法牵上新买家
Then you can't line up a new buyer,
你就没法给供应商付钱
which means you can't pay off the supplier.
沙巴兹  怎么了  老兄
Shabazz, what up, dog?
现在喝伏特加有点早啊
So, uh, it's kinda early to be drinking vodka,
但我已经和瑞安聊了
but whatever. I already rapped with Ryan.
他和戴克斯特聊过了
All right, he talked it up with Dexter,
戴克斯特还是要把生意做了
and Dexter's still down to do the deal.
好吗  他不在意他表兄的事
Okay? Regardless of what happen to his cousin,
我们还能挣一笔
we in it for good money, baby.
-好  -那么
- Yeah. - All right.
那你怎么还是不爽  你还好吗
So why you trippin', bro? You good?
因为戴克斯特提了个新要求
'Cause Dexter made a new demand.
他告诉韦斯他会一笔勾销的唯一方式就是
Told Wes the only way he'd move forward is if
以牙还牙
he evened things out.
以牙还牙  你在说什么
Evened things out-- what are you talking about?
尸体
The bodies.
韦斯说了马利克得死
Wes saying Malik has to go.
我来执行
And I gotta do it.
-等等  什么  -没错
- Wait, what? - Yeah.
我得亲手杀了我弟弟
I have to kill my little brother.
不不  你得走...
No, no, you gotta walk away--
事情不是那样做的
It don't work that way.
你知道的
You know that.
我知道你以为一切都没事了
I know you think this is gonna go away.
但并不是
But it's not.
你得醒醒了
You need to wake up.
这是你的人生
This is your life.
如果你不说出事情的真相
If you don't tell the truth about what happened,
你会死在监狱里的
you will die in prison.
我现在不想谈这件事
Look, I don't wanna talk about this now.
为什么
Why?
你不懂
Well, you don't understand.
我不懂什么
I d-don't understand what?
你不懂我
You don't understand me.
我懂  相信我
I do. Trust me.
好吧  那你为什么不停让我
All right, then why do you keep asking me
做我做不到的事
to do something that I'm not capable of?
为什么
Why?
因为尽管我们经历了这一切
'Cause despite everything we have been through,
我还爱你
I still love you.
我只是想让你也爱自己
And I just want you to love yourself.
一点就好
Just a little.
足够你意识到为汉克·博伊特牺牲你的人生
Just enough to make you realize how stupid it is
是多么愚蠢就好
to sacrifice your life for Hank Voight.
宝贝  拜托  我爱你
Listen, honey. Please, I love you.
我知道你想照顾我
And I know you're trying to look out for me.
但是我能搞定的  我可以
But I'm gonna beat this. I am.
但是我会用正确的方式搞定这件事
But I'm gonna beat it the right way,
我知道的唯一的方式
the only way that I know how.
兄弟
Hey, man.
我来看埃尔文·奥林斯基
Here to see Alvin Olinksy.
来得太晚了
You're too late.
我是情报组的汉克·博伊特警长
Listen, I'm Sergeant Hank Voight, Intelligence.
只是想和一位朋友打招呼
Just wanna say hello to a friend.
抱歉  囚犯探视时间已过
Sorry, inmate visiting hours are over.
他不是个囚犯  他是个警察
Yeah, well, he's not an inmate, he's a cop.
如果他在这里  那他就是囚犯
If he's in here, he's an inmate.
-你确定没别的办法...  -我确定
- You sure there's nothing-- - I'm sure.
但你可以明早来看看
But feel free to swing by tomorrow morning.
梅瑞狄斯  埃尔怎么样
Meredith. How's Al?
拜托  跟我说说
Come on, talk to me.
在里面的应该是你
It should be you in there.
不是他
Not him.
真令我恶心
And it makes me sick.
我希望他就是个普通人
I wish he was just a regular guy,
不是什么要遵循愚蠢的准则的人
not someone who lived by some stupid code.
那样事情就简单多了
Would make everything so much easier.
埃尔的事有什么新消息吗
Any update on Al?
新闻里到处都是这案子
Case is all over the news.
可以预料到  海莉
Yeah, I think that's to be expected, Hailey.
我只希望法官允许他保释
I just hope the judge gives him bail.
会的
He will.
谋杀的法规很严格
Well, statute for murder is pretty tough.
我说他会被允许保释的
Well, I said he will.
我不想谈埃尔的事了  明白吗
Listen, I'm done talking about Al, understand?
有人想聊聊这些M4吗
Somebody wanna talk about these M4s,
我很乐意加入
I'm happy to engage.
好吧
Well,
整个运作变得复杂得多
the whole operation just got a lot more complicated.
什么意思
What do you mean?
韦斯刚刚命令沙巴兹杀了他的小弟  马利克
Wes just ordered Shabazz to kill his little brother, Malik.
戴克斯特说只有这样他才会做这笔交易
Dexter say that's the only way he's gonna do the deal.
那沙巴兹呢
All right, so where's Shabazz on all this?
他准备执行这个命令吗
He gonna carry out the order?
当然不会了
Of course he's not gonna carry out the order.
他不想杀他的小弟
He doesn't wanna kill his little brother.
但韦斯让他这么做
But Wes told him to do it.
所以如果沙巴兹不杀马利克  那...
So if Shabazz doesn't kill Malik, then...
韦斯就杀了沙巴兹  就这么简单
Wes kills Shabazz, simple as that.
在我看来并不简单
Doesn't sound simple to me.
我们不能让他杀掉自己的血亲
We can't let this man take out his own flesh and blood,
不能那样
not like that.
为什么不能
Why not?
-你说什么  -我们要
- Excuse me? - We're about to take
清理街上的枪支
some serious guns off the street.
枪能杀很多无辜的人
Guns capable of killing a lot of innocent civilians.
代价是失去一个少年犯罪集团成员
The cost of doing that is losing one gang-banger--
沙巴兹是个好小伙  警长
Shabazz is a good dude, Sarge.
听着  我明白他在帮派里
Now listen, I understand he's in the gang.
但是他只是个被困在引擎盖里的猫
But he's just a cat from the hood that got caught up
做了错事  他不是个杀手
doing the wrong thing. He's not a killer.
霍斯特德还没被发现  目前情况很好
Halstead's still under his cover, it's still good.
-我们可以这样弄到枪  -不
- We can get the guns that way. - No.
我想你继续卧底  好吗
I want you staying under, okay?
直到沙巴兹真的对他弟动手
Until Shabazz actually moves on his brother,
一切照常
it's business as usual.
知道了
Copy that.
等等  等等
Hold up. Hold up.
给你准备了个小礼物
Got a little present for you.
是个一次性手机
It's a burner.
我看你的案子了
So I've been reading your case.
看起来你像是被陷害了
Seems like you're gettin' set up.
他们说你是为
They say you're taking the fall
宾汉姆谋杀案的人背锅了
for somebody else in this Bingham murder.
重点是如果你有要传达的消息
Point is, if you got a chit to call in
或是要出卖谁  就赶紧做
or someone to sell out, you gotta do it,
因为你在这里不安全
'cause you're not safe here.
-我是个大人了  -不管你多大
- I'm a big boy. - Don't matter how big you are,
不是在这  不是你背后有个靶子的时候
not in here, not when there's a target on your back.
我就直说了  警察对警察
Look. I'm just shooting straight, cop to cop.
但你不是个警察
But you're not a cop.
因为如果你是  你就不会这么说
'Cause if you were, you'd never say what you just said.
希望你能被保释  埃尔
Sure hope you make bail, Al.
巴兹  你一得到消息就告诉我
Bazz, soon as you get this message, bro, just call me.
好吗  在你家门口  我是拉玛
Okay? In front of your crib. This is Lamar, man.
我找你有事
I'm looking for you.
我感觉有点不对劲
My mind's feelin' a little nervous, dog.
5021I  紧急情况
5021 Ida, emergency.
菲尔莫尔南街1249号发生枪击
Shots fired at 1249 South Fillmore,
现场有便衣警察
plain-clothes officers on the scene.
你听到了吗
You hear that?
上来
We up here.
沙巴兹
Shabazz!
坚持住  兄弟  坚持住
Hold on, man, hold on.
没人
Got you.
我去后面追
I'm going out the back.
警察  5021I  黑人男性身高一米八
Police! 5021 Ida, we got a male, black, 6 feet,
黑色夹克  开着黑色SUV逃走
black jacket, fleeing in a black SUV.
没看到车牌号  沿着第46大街向西跑了
Can't get plates. Headed west-bound, down 46th.
巴兹
Bazz?
发生什么事了
What happened?
我不想孤独地死去
I don't wanna die alone.
沙巴兹  谁干的
Shabazz, who did it?
韦斯
Wes.
我做不到
I couldn't do it.
我没法杀马利克
I couldn't kill Malik.
这是因为你是个好哥哥  沙巴兹
That's because you a good brother, Shabazz.
沙巴兹死了
Shabazz is dead.
沙巴兹吗  不是马利克
Shabazz, not Malik?
刚刚在他家发现他
Just found him in his house
胸口中了两枪  因为他没法对他弟弟下手
with two in his chest 'cause he wouldn't kill his brother.
他死前跟我说是韦斯干的
Right before he died, he told me Wes did it.
我们现在就去抓他
I say we go get his ass right now.
我们要先查出那批M4
Not until we smoke out the M4s.
他是凶手  警长  这是死者说的
He's a killer, Sarge. We got a dead man's word.
我们会因为谋杀拿下韦斯
Look, we will nail Wes for murder
但要先找到枪  明白吗
after we get the guns, understand?
-喂  -怎么
- Hey. - What?
戴克斯特刚才跟我说韦斯给他发了一张
Dexter just told me that Wes sent him a picture
沙巴兹胸口中了一枪的照片
of Shabazz with a bullet in his chest.
看到没  这就证明他完成了交易条件
See, that's proof he delivered his end of the bargain,
也就是说交易继续生效
which means the deal's back on.
是的  他们一小时后在老嘉元仓库见面
Yeah, they're meeting at the old Kagen warehouse in an hour.
好的  让其他队员加快速度
All right, get the rest of the team up to speed.
我们在仓库见
Let's meet over at the warehouse.
你行吗
You good?
行  去抓他们吧
Yeah, I'm good. Let's get 'em.
好的  我让霍斯特德跟戴克斯特一起去了
Okay, I got Halstead arriving with Dexter.
现场待命
Just stand by.
视线不佳  换个更好的位置
No eyes, moving for a better position.
我们在后面就位了
We're in position in the back.
警长  奥林斯基的事
Sarge, this Olinsky thing.
我无法想象对你来说有多难
Can't imagine how hard it must be.
-如果你需要...  -我只需要你
- If you need something-- - I just need you
做好自己的分内事  海莉  这样就行
to do your job, Hailey, that's all.
韦斯到了  等我信号
Wes is arriving. Wait for my signal.
好的  游戏开始了  所以枪在这里对吗
All right. Game on. So the guns are here, right?
搞什么
Hell nah.
马利克来这里干什么
What's Malik doing here, man?
-马利克  -是的
- Malik? - Yeah.
他不知道他哥哥死了
He don't know his brother's dead.
或者他不知道站在他旁边的人杀了他
Or that he's standing next to the guy that killed him.
-好哥们  韦斯  -你就是戴克斯特吧
- My man, Wes. - Hey. You must be Dexter.
他来这里干什么
What's he doing here?
这是我的事
Oh, that's my business.
他会管好自己吗
He gonna behave himself?
只要你没事  我也没事
I'm cool as long as you are.
东西带来了吗
You got the product, man?
钱带来了吗
You got the money?
我得先看看货
I need to see the product first.
过来吧  表演时间
Come on over. Showtime.
-不  -怎么
- No. - What?
有人杀了我哥
Somebody shot my brother.
我很遗憾  兄弟  真的
I'm sorry to hear that, man. I really am.
但现在我们还有正事要做  好吗
But right now, we got some business to handle, all right?
你在笑什么
What you smirking at?
没什么
Nothing.
警长  有一辆蓝色面包车开过来了
Sarge, we got a blue van approaching.
面包车开过来了  蓝色
Okay, van is approaching, blue.
我们等它停车然后听我指示行动
We wait for it to park and move in on my signal.
你个狗...你杀了
You mother--you killed--
沉住气  冷静  冷静
Take it easy, chill, chill!
有枪  枪  枪  枪
We got a gun. Gun, gun, gun.
马上行动
Move in, now.
快快快
Go, go, go.
芝加哥警察  别动
Chicago PD, don't move!
芝加哥警察  放下武器
Chicago PD, drop your weapon!
警察  放下  戴克斯特
Police! Put it down, Dexter.
放下包
Drop the bag.
安东尼奥  注意  蓝色面的朝你开过去了
Antonio, heads-up, blue van heading your way.
下车
Get out of the van!
手举起来  下车
Let me see your hands! Get out of the van!
金  安东尼奥  你们没事吧
Kim! Antonio, are you good?
我们没事
Yeah, we're good!
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
-真不敢相信你是个警察  -我的错
- Can't believe you a cop. - My bad, dog.
有时候就是这样
It be like that sometimes.
-谁杀了我哥  -你
- Who killed my brother? - You did.
-什么  -你
- What? - You did.
你在说什么  这事跟我一点关系都没有
What you talkin' about? I ain't have nothing to do with that.
哥们  如果你没出纰漏
Brother, if you would have kept it 100 from the jump,
而且没狡辩  那巴兹就不会死了
and admitted to it, then Bazz wouldn't be dead.
死的就是你
You would.
这不能怪我吧
Can't put that on me.
就怪你
I just did.
不敢相信我们真走到了这一步
I can't believe we're really here.
不会有事的
Gonna be fine.
那边
Right there.
全体起立
All rise.
本庭现在开庭
Court is now in session.
默多克法官负责主持
The honorable Judge Maddox presiding.
请就坐
You may be seated.
伊利诺伊州起诉埃尔文·奥林斯基
State of Illinois vs. Alvin Olinsky.
二级谋杀  案件号542234
Murder in the second degree, case #542234.
奥沙先生
Mr. Osha?
法官阁下  考虑到案件的性质
Your Honor, given the serious nature of the charge,
以及被告当警察多年
and the fact that the defendant was a veteran police officer
对犯罪执法体系了如指掌
with unique knowledge of the criminal justice system,
并且可以接触到秘密线人
as well as having access to confidential informants
和有组织犯罪集团成员
and members of organized crime syndicates,
我们认为他极有可能逃走
we believe he poses a significant flight risk.
所以  我们请求不予保释
And as such, we would request that no bail be set,
被告一直关押于
and that the defendant be remanded
库克县监狱  直至审判
to Cook County Jail until trial.
玛奈提先生
Mr. Manetti?
法官阁下  州的请求
Your Honor, the state's request
既荒谬又具惩罚性
is both preposterous and punitive.
这个案子根本站不住脚
This case is built on sand.
埃尔文·奥林斯基和谋杀被害人
The only evidence connecting Alvin Olinsky
唯一相联系的证据是一缕头发
to the homicide victim is a single strand of hair
以及一个有毒瘾的目击证人的证词
and the testimony of a drug-addled witness.
所以  把奥林斯基先生关在监狱
As such, to hold Mr. Olinsky in prison
来换取某种认罪协议  这是不合理的
to leverage some sort of plea bargain is unconscionable.
再说了  奥林斯基先生为芝加哥人民
Moreover, Mr. Olinsky's put his life on the line
出生入死三十多年
for the people of this city for over 30 years.
玛奈提先生  这是听证会  不是结案陈词
Mr. Manetti, this is a bond hearing, not a closing argument.
被告将被关押于库克县监狱
Defendant is remanded into the custody of
等待审判
the Cook County Jail, pending trial.
下一个案子
Next case.
伊利诺伊州起诉胡安·莫拉诺
The state of Illinois vs. Juan Medrano.
-持械枪击  案件号3320843  -走
- Aggravated robbery case #3320843. - Let's go.
-不好意思  有什么需要帮助  -我自己来
- Excuse me, can I help you? - I got it.
-你去哪里了  -我给你打电话了
- Where the hell were you? - Hey, I tried to call you.
我们说好了的
We had a deal!
你小声点  天啊
Keep your voice down, for God's sake.
-我已经尽力了  -还不够好
- I did everything that I could. - Well, it wasn't good enough!
格拉德查克法官称病请假时
When Judge Gladchuck called in sick,
市长打电话让他指定默多克法官
the Mayor called him, told him to appoint Judge Maddox.
-市长  -对
- The Mayor. - Yes.
-市长打给了格拉德查克  -对
- The Mayor called Gladchuck. - Yeah.
我猜是伍兹嗅到了味道
My guess is, Woods smelled a rat.
所以想确保有正确的法官
Wanted to make sure that he had the right judge in there
负责听证会
for the bail hearing.
我们能上诉吗
Well--I mean, can we appeal the ruling?
能  不过...
Yes, but... You know.
我们反败为胜的概率接近于零
Our odds of prevailing are close to zero.
那埃尔就只能待在监狱里等审判
So Al just stays in custody till trial?
对  这是原告想要的结果
Yeah. Yeah, it's what the prosecution wants.
下一步怎么办  警长
All right, so what's the next step, Sarge?
你跟埃尔或者他的律师谈过了吗
Did you talk to Al or his lawyer?
他会上诉吗
Is he gonna appeal the bond hearing?
他会上诉吗  喂
Is he gonna appeal the bond hearing--hey!
我问你问题
I asked you a question!
好了
Okay,
埃尔会出来的
Al's gonna be out of there.
很快  马上
Soon. Real soon.
-好吗  -什么意思
- Okay? - What's that mean?
意思是我在处理
It means I'm taking care of things,
但我现在不能说细节
but I can't get into the details right now.
为什么
Why not?
谢谢你的关心
I appreciate your concern.
不过你得就此打住了
But you gotta back off now.
我想知道怎么做才能帮埃尔
I wanna know what I need to do to help Al.
你告诉我们的就只有...
And all I'm hearing from you is nothing--
因为你不知道你在说什么
Because you don't know what you're talking about!
-放开  不是吧  -大家都知道...
- Get off! Really? - Everyone knows--
-说话小心点  -够了  够了
- Watch yourself! - Enough! Enough.
就是他
There he is.
此时此地不行  继续走
Not here, not today. Keep moving.
我让你们继续走
I said, keep moving!
你在想什么  汉克
So what's on your mind, Hank?
奥林斯基
Olinsky.
该把事情处理一下了
It's time to set things straight.
我同意
Sounds good to me.
你从头到尾跟我说说
Why don't you walk me through everything that happened,
事情的经过吧
from beginning to end.
我会的
I will.
首先  我想要你的保证
First, I want some assurances.
明天一早  释放奥林斯基
Olinsky is released, first thing in the morning.
不会再有其它罪名起诉他
No other charges are filed against him.
或者任何人
Or anyone else.
我可以做到
I can do that...
不过是等听完你的话之后
After I hear what you have to say.
如果有说服力  那我就打给检察官
If it's compelling, I'll call the prosecutor
然后正式释放奥林斯基
and we will make it official.
好  那就来吧
All right, let's do this.
所以我才让你早回来  埃尔
That's why I wanted you to walk back early, Al.
那些人就是禽兽
These guys are animals.
-你没事吧  -没事
- You okay? - Yeah, I'm good.
未完待续